Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 2-19; I; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
  - Individual Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 19; A; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
    - A Child's Christmas in Wales (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2001 November 23-December 9; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - The Crucible (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 February 1-16; (1 of 5); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - The Crucible (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 February 1-16; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - The Crucible (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 February 1-16; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - The Crucible (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 February 1-16; (4 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - The Crucible (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 February 1-16; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - The Three Sisters (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 March 1-16; (1 of 4); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - The Three Sisters (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 March 1-16; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - The Three Sisters (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 March 1-16; (3 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - The Three Sisters (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 March 1-16; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (1 of 11); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (2 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (3 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (4 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (5 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (6 of 11); (Production Materials) (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (7 of 11); (Production Materials) (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (8 of 11); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (9 of 11); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (10 of 11); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Oklahoma! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 April 12-27; (11 of 11); (Financial Materials) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (1 of 7); (Playbill and Press Clipping) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (4 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (5 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - All in the Timing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 May 31-June 15; (7 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - As You Like It (Appalachian Shakespeare Project), 2002 June; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - As You Like It (Appalachian Shakespeare Project), 2002 June; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (1 of 7); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (4 of 7); (Photographs and Negatives) (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (5 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Art (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 August 30-September 14; (7 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Nora (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 October 11-27; (1 of 4); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Nora (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 October 11-27; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Nora (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 October 11-27; (3 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Nora (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 October 11-27; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (1 of 8); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (2 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (3 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (4 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (5 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (6 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (7 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2002 November 22-December 8; (8 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Bacchae of Euripides (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 7-22; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Bacchae of Euripides (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 7-22; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - The Bacchae of Euripides (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 7-22; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The Bacchae of Euripides (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 7-22; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - The Bacchae of Euripides (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 7-22; (5 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - The Bacchae of Euripides (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 7-22; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (1 of 7); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (4 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (5 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Midwives (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 February 28-March 15; (7 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (1 of 8); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (2 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (3 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (4 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (5 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (6 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (7 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 April 11-26; (8 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Macbeth (Piccolo Spoleto Festival; Festival d'Avignon), 2003 May 24-June 7, July 5-20; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Macbeth (Piccolo Spoleto Festival; Festival d'Avignon), 2003 May 24-June 7, July 5-20; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Pump Boys and Dinettes (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 May 30-June 14; (1 of 5); (Playbill) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Pump Boys and Dinettes (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 May 30-June 14; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Pump Boys and Dinettes (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 May 30-June 14; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Pump Boys and Dinettes (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 May 30-June 14; (4 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Pump Boys and Dinettes (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 May 30-June 14; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Always...Patsy Cline (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 August 29-September 13; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers and Play Newsletter) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Always...Patsy Cline (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 August 29-September 13; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Always...Patsy Cline (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 August 29-September 13; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Always...Patsy Cline (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 August 29-September 13; (4 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Always...Patsy Cline (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 August 29-September 13; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Always...Patsy Cline (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 August 29-September 13; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Proof (Clarence Brown Lab Theatre), 2003 September 13-21; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Proof (Clarence Brown Lab Theatre), 2003 September 13-21; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Buried Child (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 October 10-25; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Buried Child (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 October 10-25; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Buried Child (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 October 10-25; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Buried Child (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 October 10-25; (4 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Buried Child (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 October 10-25; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (1 of 13); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (2 of 13); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (3 of 13); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (4 of 13); (Photographs) (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (5 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (6 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (7 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (8 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (9 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (10 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (11 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (12 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - The Secret Garden (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2003 November 21-December 7; (13 of 13); (Production Materials) (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (1 of 7); (Playbills, Press Clippings, Postcards, and Play Newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (4 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (5 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 January 30-February 14; (7 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (1 of 7); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (4 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (5 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - The Road to Mecca (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 February 27-March 13; (7 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 April 16-May 1; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 April 16-May 1; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 April 16-May 1; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 April 16-May 1; (4 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 April 16-May 1; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Scenes from an Execution (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 April 23-25; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Scenes from an Execution (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 April 23-25; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Babel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 June 11-20; (1 of 6); (Playbill, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Babel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 June 11-20; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Babel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 June 11-20; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Babel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 June 11-20; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Babel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 June 11-20; (5 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Babel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 June 11-20; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - The Dresser (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 August 26-September 11; (1 of 2); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - The Dresser (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 August 26-September 11; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Anna Karenina (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 October 7-24; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Anna Karenina (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 October 7-24; (2 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Anna Karenina (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 October 7-24; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Anna Karenina (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 October 7-24; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (1 of 9); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (2 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (3 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (4 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (5 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (6 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (7 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (8 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2004 November 4-20; (9 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - The Odd Couple (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 January 27-February 12; (1 of 4); (Playbill and Play Newsletter) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - The Odd Couple (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 January 27-February 12; (2 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - The Odd Couple (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 January 27-February 12; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - The Odd Couple (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 January 27-February 12; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Sing Down the Moon, 2005 February; (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Metamorphoses (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2005 February 24-March 12; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletters) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Metamorphoses (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2005 February 24-March 12; (2 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Metamorphoses (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2005 February 24-March 12; (3 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Metamorphoses (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2005 February 24-March 12; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Metamorphoses (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2005 February 24-March 12; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - All the Way Home (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 April 7-23; (1 of 5); (Playbill and Play Newsletters) (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - All the Way Home (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 April 7-23; (2 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - All the Way Home (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 April 7-23; (3 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - All the Way Home (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 April 7-23; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - All the Way Home (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 April 7-23; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 August 26-September 11; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletters) (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 August 26-September 11; (2 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 August 26-September 11; (3 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 August 26-September 11; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 August 26-September 11; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - The Trojan Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 October 20-November 6; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - The Trojan Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 October 20-November 6; (2 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - The Trojan Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 October 20-November 6; (3 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - The Trojan Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 October 20-November 6; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - The Trojan Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 October 20-November 6; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 December 1-23; (1 of 2); (Playbill, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2005 December 1-23; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 February 2-19; (1 of 2); (Playbill, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 February 2-19; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - A Night of Absurdities: The Interview; Orgasmo Adulto Escapes from the Zoo, 2006 February 17-19; (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Stones in his Pocket (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2006 March 2-19; (1 of 5); (Playbill, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Stones in his Pocket (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2006 March 2-19; (2 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Stones in his Pocket (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2006 March 2-19; (3 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Stones in his Pocket (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2006 March 2-19; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Stones in his Pocket (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2006 March 2-19; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Big River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 April 13-30; (1 of 5); (Playbill, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletter) (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Big River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 April 13-30; (2 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Big River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 April 13-30; (3 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Big River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 April 13-30; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Big River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 April 13-30; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 August 24-September 10; (1 of 4); (Playbills, Press Clippings, and Play Newsletters) (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 August 24-September 10; (2 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 2006 August 24-September 10; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 29, Folder 26)